srisankaramatrimony.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy | Sri Sankara Matrimony - srisankaramatrimony.com

As a matrimonial network, we are constantly striving to give our customers the best quality matrimonial services solely bearing your satisfaction in mind. Indeed we are firmly committed to your right to privacy and with all the respective terms. Here are some of the privacy statements which are pertinent to the information we gather from you.

Please use the website only if you agree to these terms and conditions. In the event that you disagree with any of them, please refrain from using the services on the Website.

#### The Information we Require from our Customers

As the base requirement, we collect some of the basic information from our customers who intend to enjoy a range of services our website offers.

Some of the details you should fill in are the FIRST NAME, LAST NAME, MOBILE NUMBER, E-MAIL ADDRESS, MAILING ADDRESS, A USER-SPECIFIED PASSWORD, FAX NUMBER or TELEPHONE NUMBER, and ZIP CODE.

In case you wish to create a credit account with us to make your payment fee, we require your CREDIT CARD NUMBER, A BILLING ADDRESS, YOUR CREDIT CARD EXPIRY DATE, and IN CASE PAYMENT IS MADE BY CHEQUE OR DEMAND DRAFT THE ADDRESS DETAILS ARE COLLECTED.

Do not worry about the process of your credit card transactions as we take all measures to secure your credit card information.

You may decide to publish some information in order to use the services on our website. We are not responsible for the manner in which third parties use your personal information that you voluntarily publish on the website.

Please note that we cannot verify the information you provide and you will be deemed to have provided accurate information. We are not liable if any personal information provided by you is incorrect.

#### Information that we collect automatically

When you access our website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. "Cookies" are small text files transferred from our Website to your hard drive that recognize repeat users, track use behaviour, and facilitate your access to and use of our Website. These "cookies" do not harm files nor do they allow anyone to access your personally identifiable information - they simply allow us to adjust information and advertisements to help your visit to be more pleasant and relevant.

Information that is collected via IP Address and cookie technologies is not personally identifiable. However, if you provide personally identifiable information as above on our website, this information may be linked to the data stored in these technologies.

#### The way we use the information we receive

We will use your personally identifiable information to provide you with the services you may have specifically requested or to process and maintain your account. We may also use this information to contact you concerning your account or for customer service purposes. We share personally identifiable information with our partners when that is necessary to do so to provide the services or features you have requested.

We use your IP address and cookie information to collect demographic statistics about our users, and to display information and advertisements that match your interests and profile. We may share aggregate information (not individual) about use statistics and demographic information with advertisers and other third parties. Personal information about you as an individual will not be provided to any third party without your consent.

In addition to the above uses, all personally identifiable information and/or the personally identifiable information of any third party may also be divulged (i) in compliance with an order from a court of law or government summons, sanction, or order; (ii) as otherwise required by law; or (iii) when we strongly believe that you have violated its terms of use or privacy policy, or the property or the safety of you or any other individual are at risk. We will not be responsible for any personal information that you share with other members of this website or with other third parties in relation to the services offered herein.

#### Notice

We are entitled make changes to the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions contained herein from time to time and solely at our discretion. You will be notified of the changes and the modified Privacy Policy or / and the Terms and Conditions would be binding and effective upon all existing users of our website and you shall be deemed to have accepted such changes, should you continue using the website. Should you not concur with the changed terms upon being notified, you should forthwith stop using our services and/or unsubscribe from membership.
